# KEYONNA JACKSON

2317 Scushman ave Tacoma, Wa 9713029789

keyonnajackson537@gmail.com

#### Career overview

I am looking for a position that I can show off my skills in. I am very dependable and a quick learner. I am currently a caregiver been doing it for about 6 years, I'm looking for something I can grow in and extend my education level. I will bring your company somebody they can rely on and someone your other employees can always look up to as a role model and bring in different work ethics.

### **Employment history:**

#### Personal Caretaker - First choice Tacoma, Wa

August 2020- Current

- worked with clients with dementia, memory loss

- Bed bound clients
  changed diapers
  feeding
  light house keeping
  appointments

#### Caregiver - Puget sound assisted living Tacoma, Wa

August 2019-December 2020

- changing there depens
- Feeding
- Meal prep /cooking

## Caregiver - Sapphire liberty pointe portland or.

March 2019 - July 2020

Caregiver - Trinity LLC - Tacoma, Wa

January 2021-Current

## Education:

Fir Ridge Highschool diploma Class of 2016

## Skills:

- Ability to work well with others
- Prep and plan my work
- organization skills
- Finance statements
- resilency under pressure
- time management
- communication
- patients

- knowledge of proper cash handling
- strong mathematics
- customer service

## References:

Esther K : 253-625-1265 Kayla : 503-707-0367 Kaylan: 971-207-3981